# **SERGIO LOMBANA**

# **Software Developer**

- 4168268035
  sergiolombana101@gmail.com
  Toronto
- http://portfolio-9909.herokuapp.com/

### **SUMMARY**

Computer Programming undergrad with excellent communication skills and 4+ years of experience seeking an industry opportunity to put into practice the knowledge acquired during college studies. Hard-working, time-effective and detail-oriented individual. Looking for a company to demonstrate skills and benefit their processes.

## **PROJECTS**

# **Inventory Management System**

 MEAN stack application in charge of managing Shiva Exports Ltda inventory processes. Built with high quantity of JavaScript to provide user interactivity.
 Project was built using all the Agile Methodologies process.

### **React Productivity Assistant**

 React Native Mobile Application used to organize user's schedule, events and track habits. Built with node.js as the server language and MongoDB for data persistence.

# **Customer Satisfaction Management System**

- Built using Angular. The Management System takes care of handling customer feedback and reviews about company's products. It creates tickets for Admin to review and organize.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Computer Programmer Analyst** 

2018 - 2020

**George Brown College** 

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

React

CSS

GIT

NodeJS

Angular

Bootstrap

JavaScript

• HTML

• Data Science

AWS

JQuery

MySQL

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **Computer Programming Tutor**

**George Brown College** 

09/2019 - 04/2020 - Toronto

- Helped student with Web Development queries
- Created programming challenges for students weekly

### Student Advisor (Peer-coach)

**George Brown College** 

09/2018 - 04/2020 - Toronto

- Tutored web programming students
- Delivered workshops on soft skills
- Advised students on Resume writing strategies

### Waiter

Fukui Sushi

06/2019 - 09/2019 - Toronto

- Took customers orders
- Ensured restaurant was following cleaning procedures.